[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The grizzly bear is a subspecies of the brown bear.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bazooka introduced the first bubble gum comics named Bazooka Joe. It was first introduced in this year.", "correct_answer": "1953", "incorrect_answers": ["1920", "1910", "1963"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What exactly is the Felix Felicis in the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, one of the most expensive films ever made?", "correct_answer": "Potion of luck", "incorrect_answers": ["A love potion", "A magic mirror that shows ones true self", "A wise cat who knows the deepest secrets of the Universe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Saturday Night Fever, this character, portrayed by Barry Miller, fell off the bridge and died.", "correct_answer": "Bobby", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank", "Enzo", "Gino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the South American snake Lachesis muta, commonly known as South American bushmaster, do when it feels threatened?", "correct_answer": "It starts vibrating its tail.", "incorrect_answers": ["It spreads its neck.", "It hisses and dances.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the web address http://www.microsoft.com, the com at the end means what?", "correct_answer": "Commercial", "incorrect_answers": ["Complicated", "Communication", "Compensated"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of the magnificent 7 are killed in the movie Guns of the Magnificent Seven.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1977 William Friedkin released this remake of the 1953 French film Le Salaire de la Peur. Steve McQueen was the directors first choice for the film.", "correct_answer": "Sorcerer", "incorrect_answers": ["Network", "All the Presidents Men", "Cruising"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the gin rummy game you should never pick up a speculative discard. That is, you should never pick up a discard without using it in a meld.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1991 biopic about a popular rock band was directed by Oliver Stone?", "correct_answer": "The Doors", "incorrect_answers": ["The Rolling Stones", "Deep Purple", "The Beatles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This unit, named after the German physicist who discovered the relation between voltage and current, is the basic unit of electrical resistance.", "correct_answer": "Ohm", "incorrect_answers": ["Watt", "Frequency", "Resistor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1939 movie The Wizard of Oz is based on which novel by L. Frank Baum?", "correct_answer": "The Wonderful Wizard of Oz", "incorrect_answers": ["Dorothys Adventures in Oz", "The Land of Oz", "The Wizard of Oz"]}]